<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FAQ on</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/</link><description>Recent content in FAQ on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/0-what-is-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/0-what-is-localstack/</guid><description>LocalStack is a platform that simplifies and accelerates development of cloud applications. At its core, LocalStack provides a cloud service emulation layer that runs in a single container on your laptop or in your CI environment. With LocalStack, you can run your AWS services or Lambdas entirely on your local machine without connecting to a remote cloud provider.
LocalStack focuses on developer experience (DevX) and offers a number of team collaboration features on top of the core emulation layer, like advanced persistence mechanisms that allow reuse and sharing of resources among team members and across environments.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/1-available-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/1-available-services/</guid><description>The overview of different usage tiers (Open Source, Pro, Enterprise) can be found at LocalStack Features page
You can check the latest details about the current feature coverage of the specific services you want to use here: LocalStack Features coverage.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/2-types-of-licenses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/2-types-of-licenses/</guid><description>We currently offer three types of licenses:
LocalStack Pro: Individual User Licenses: Individual user licenses are used on the individual users local machines (they offer unlimited use of LocalStack Pro on the individual developers local machines).
LocalStack Pro - CI Licenses: For using LocalStack Pro in CI environments and shared cloud resources you require a LocalStack Pro CI license key. Only one CI key is required and can be configured across all CI environments, but you have the option to setup different CI keys for usage tracking purposes at no additional cost.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/3-commercial-use/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/3-commercial-use/</guid><description>Yes, the Community Edition can be used for commercial use (distributed under the Apache 2.0 open source license).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/4-tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/4-tools/</guid><description>The list of tool integrations supported by LocalStack can be found at LocalStack integration page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/5-slack-invite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/5-slack-invite/</guid><description>Users receive an invite after signing up to the LocalStack app on app.localstack.cloud. Otherwise please reach out to info@localstack.cloud.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/6-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/6-free-trial/</guid><description>Yes, we offer a 14 days free trial. To activate your free trial, sign up on the app app.localstack.cloud. Under the billing section click on create a new plan.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/7-invoices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/7-invoices/</guid><description>You can find your entire invoice history in your account details at Account billing section.
Please note, if you are part of an organization account, only your organization’s admins have access to the billing section.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/8-cancel-trial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/8-cancel-trial/</guid><description>Your free trial will automatically expire after 14 days - no need to manually cancel it. We do not automatically add a paid license at the end of the free trial.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/9-more-licenses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/9-more-licenses/</guid><description>You can create new subscriptions on Account billing section by using the + ADD NEW PLAN button.
Please note, if you are part of an organization account, only your organization’s admins have access to the billing section and can assign API keys to you in the member section at Account members section.</description></item></channel></rss>