<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LocalStack on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in LocalStack on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Features</title><link>/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 18:56:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>/features/</guid><description>The figure below provides an overview of the different usage tiers (Open Source, Pro, Enterprise), and the features provided by each tier.
Open Source The Open Source edition of LocalStack provides the following core Cloud APIs on your local machine.
ACM API Gateway CloudFormation CloudWatch CloudWatch Logs DynamoDB DynamoDB Streams EC2 Elasticsearch Service EventBridge (CloudWatch Events) Firehose IAM Kinesis KMS Lambda Redshift Route53 S3 SecretsManager SES SNS SQS SSM StepFunctions STS Pro In addition to the above, the Pro version of LocalStack supports additional APIs and advanced features, including:</description></item><item><title>Solutions</title><link>/solutions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:56:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>/solutions/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Community</title><link>/community/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 08:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/community/</guid><description>We at LocalStack value our community greatly. Therefore, we offer a wide variety to keep in touch with us, whether you want to get involved, or simply want to stay informed on the newest updates regarding your favorite local cloud emulator.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>/faq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/faq/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Free Educational License</title><link>/educational-license/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/educational-license/</guid><description>LocalStack Education License helps you learn and gain AWS skills and expertise through LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s fully functional local AWS cloud stack.
Students and educators can get free 6 months educational access to LocalStack, renewable as long as you remain eligible. Students need to be enrolled in an accredited educational program that takes one or more years of full-time study to complete.
How can LocalStack Education License help you?
Get access to all features on the community and professional edition of LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Terms and Conditions</title><link>/terms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 14:52:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/terms/</guid><description>Terms and Conditions By using the LocalStack Platform or LocalStack App (&amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;), or any other service operated by its owner LocalStack GmbH of Switzerland (&amp;ldquo;LocalStack&amp;rdquo;), the person or organization (&amp;ldquo;Customer&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo;) is agreeing to be bound by the following terms and conditions (&amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;). By accepting these Terms, signing an Order, or using the Services, you represent that you are of legal age and have the authority to bind the Customer to the Order and these Terms.</description></item><item><title>Jobs</title><link>/jobs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:40:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>/jobs/</guid><description>ALL JOBS TECH ADMINISTRATIVE GO TO MARKET</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 14:52:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.
Definitions For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:
You means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>/blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/</guid><description>ALL TOPICS NEWS SHOWCASE TUTORIAL</description></item><item><title>Pricing</title><link>/pricing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pricing/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:25:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Getting in touch Below you can find some pointers for contacting us, as well as getting in touch with the community.
Issues and Bug Reports For any bug reports, please first consult the main Github repository: https://github.com/localstack/localstack. Chances are that a similar issue may have already been posted by other users in the past. Github has an excellent search function, which may help find existing answers to your questions.
If you cannot find a solution in the existing issues, please raise a bug report directly in Github.</description></item><item><title>Products</title><link>/products/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:25:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>/products/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>