<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LocalStack on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in LocalStack on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jobs</title><link>/jobs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:40:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>/jobs/</guid><description>We are looking for top-notch people to support us in our journey in becoming the world&amp;rsquo;s leading platform to support efficient dev&amp;amp;test loops for cloud applications. Let&amp;rsquo;s make Cloud development fun again!
Here are some of our current openings.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 14:52:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.
Definitions For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:
You means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>/blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Docs</title><link>/docs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Pricing</title><link>/pricing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pricing/</guid><description>LocalStack comes in two flavors - as a free, open source Community Edition, and as a Pro Edition with extended features and support. See the table below for a comparison. If you need support for large organizations, please contact us for the Enterprise Edition.
We are strongly committed to our open source offering. Our philosophy is that today&amp;rsquo;s best software is built by great people in an open collaboration, and therefore we will continue to contribute significantly to the Community Edition of LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:25:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Getting in touch Below you can find some pointers for contacting us, as well as getting in touch with the community.
Issues and Bug Reports For any bug reports, please first consult the main Github repository: https://github.com/localstack/localstack. Chances are that a similar issue may have already been posted by other users in the past. Github has an excellent search function, which may help find existing answers to your questions.
If you cannot find a solution in the existing issues, please raise a bug report directly in Github.</description></item></channel></rss>