<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Documentation on</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/</link><description>Recent content in Documentation on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 19:01:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/introduction/</guid><description>What is LocalStack? LocalStack provides an easy-to-use test/mocking framework for developing Cloud applications. It spins up a testing environment on your local machine that provides the same functionality and APIs as the real AWS cloud environment.
You can run your Lambda functions, store data to DynamoDB tables, feed events through Kinesis streams, put your application behind an API Gateway, and much more. And all this happens on your local machine, without ever talking to the cloud.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 19:01:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/installation/</guid><description>Prerequisites Docker: The recommended way of installing LocalStack is using Docker Python: Required to install the localstack command-line interface (CLI) Installation The easiest way to install LocalStack is via pip:
pip install localstack You can then list the available commands:
localstack --help Note: If the command localstack is not available after successfully installing the package, please ensure that the folder containing pip binaries is configured in your $PATH.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 18:56:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/features/</guid><description>Features Overview The figure below provides an overview of the different usage tiers (Open Source, Pro, Enterprise), and the features provided by each tier.
Available Services LocalStack Pro spins up the following core Cloud APIs on your local machine.
Please note: Starting with version 0.11.0, all services are exposed via a single edge service endpoint - http://localhost:4566 by default. (The old service-specific port numbers from previous releases are now deprecated and disabled.</description></item><item><title>Pro Features</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 19:01:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/docs/documentation/pro/</guid><description>Features Overview The Pro version of LocalStack includes, among others, the following features:
Support for Lambda Layers Support for Relational Database Service (RDS) Support for ElastiCache Support for ECS Support for ECR Support for EKS Support for IoT APIs Support for XRay Tracing Support for Cognito Authentication Support for Athena Support for Elastic MapReduce (EMR) Support for API Gateway V2 Support for CloudFront Support for AppSync Support for SageMaker Support for Glue Support for Amplify Support for Route53 Support for Transfer Support for Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB) Support for SMTP in Simple Email Service (SES) Support for CodeCommit Support for Kinesis Data Analytics Support for IAM Security Enforcement Local Cloud Pods Multi-Region Support Multi-Account Setups Test Report Dashboards Lambda Layers Lambda layers are a new AWS feature that allows to pull in additional code and content into your Lambda functions.</description></item></channel></rss>