<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorial on</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/tags/tutorial/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorial on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 08:53:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/tags/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Monitor your failing Lambdas with CloudWatch and LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-25-cloudwatch-metric-alarms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-25-cloudwatch-metric-alarms/</guid><description>AWS CloudWatch is a service that enables monitoring of your AWS infrastructure by collecting logs and operational metrics of your deployment. An integral part of infrastructure operations is reacting in real-time to anomalous changes in metrics, e.g., spiking disk or CPU usage or failures in your serverless functions. This is where CloudWatch metric alarms and actions come into play, which you can now develop and test using LocalStack!</description></item><item><title>Debug Lambda functions from your IDE using LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-09-debug-your-lamda-functions-from-your-ide-using-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 05:08:41 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-09-debug-your-lamda-functions-from-your-ide-using-localstack/</guid><description>In the previous blog, we checked out how to hot-swap Lambda functions locally using LocalStack. Using LocalStack, you can execute your Lambda functions locally without the need to deploy them to AWS. This is a great way to test your code and learn more about how your Lambda functions work before deploying them to AWS. But there is always a question about debugging the Lambda functions from your IDE before deploying it.</description></item><item><title>Develop and Test Real-time Data Pipelines with LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-04-develop-and-test-data-analytics-pipelines-on-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-04-develop-and-test-data-analytics-pipelines-on-localstack/</guid><description>At LocalStack, we rely on AWS Lambda as a key part of our serverless infrastructure toolkit. As with any critical service, we want to extract analytics event data from running Lambda functions and aggregate it in our data warehouse so that we can track user stories and squash bugs. But this presents a challenge: how can we emit detailed analytics data while keeping Lambda code simple and performant?</description></item><item><title>Hot Swapping Python Lambda Functions using LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-03-07-hot-swapping-python-lambda-functions-using-localstack/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 08:53:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-03-07-hot-swapping-python-lambda-functions-using-localstack/</guid><description>AWS Lambda is a Serverless Function as a Service (FaaS) system that allows you to write code in your favorite programming language and run it on the AWS ecosystem. Unlike deploying your code on a server, you can now break down your application into many independent functions and deploy them as a singular units. With the help of AWS Lambda, you can strive for more modular code that can be tested and debugged while integrated with the AWS infrastructure and your core system.</description></item></channel></rss>