<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/tags/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 14:48:49 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Announcing LocalStack 1.0 General Availability!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-07-13-announcing-localstack-v1-general-availability/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 11:00:55 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-07-13-announcing-localstack-v1-general-availability/</guid><description>Today, we are excited to announce the general availability of LocalStack 1.0. This major release is a significant milestone towards our vision to propel developer productivity - by allowing dev teams to quickly and conveniently develop &amp;amp; test their cloud applications locally and across the CI/CD pipeline.
At LocalStack, we&amp;rsquo;re working to provide a better way to develop and test your cloud applications. Our platform is redefining cloud development by enabling a highly efficient, fully local development &amp;amp; testing loop and giving developers back control over their environments.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack and AWS Parity Explained</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-04-parity-explained/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-04-parity-explained/</guid><description>Parity for LocalStack means that when you, as a cloud developer, make an AWS API call to LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s cloud emulator, it behaves the same way AWS would.
Keeping parity with AWS has been our mission at LocalStack since day one. This is essential for building a reliable cloud emulator that provides a great experience for cloud application developers.
Recently we introduced new mechanisms to scale the endeavor and ensure that the parity of LocalStack with AWS increases continuously over time while keeping our service implementations up-to-date.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Pods - Enabling state sharing and team collaboration for local cloud development</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-26-cloud-pods/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-26-cloud-pods/</guid><description>Background: Ephemeral and persistent state in LocalStack By default, the state of all services in LocalStack is ephemeral - i.e., whenever you restart the LocalStack Docker container, it presents a fresh instance with a clean state that can be used to create your application resources locally. This is the default mode, which is optimized for quick experimentation, and frequent container restarts, making sure to always start with a clean slate.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack Extensions</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:51:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</guid><description>With the LocalStack 1.0 General Availability going live last month, we announced LocalStack Extensions! LocalStack Extensions allow users to extend and customize LocalStack using pluggable Python distributions.
Setting up LocalStack Extensions LocalStack Extensions is part of our Pro offering. To get started with using LocalStack Extensions, first log in to your account using the LocalStack CLI:
$ localstack login Please provide your login credentials below Username: .</description></item><item><title>Contribute to Open Source With LocalStack &amp; Hacktoberfest</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-10-01-contribute-to-open-source-with-localstack-hacktoberfest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-10-01-contribute-to-open-source-with-localstack-hacktoberfest/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s October 2022, and we have a few surprises already in store for our open-source community. LocalStack is participating in Hacktoberfest 2022, a month-long open-source program to promote and bolster open-source contribution and collaboration! We are opening up projects to contribute to for our first Hacktoberfest, and we are incredibly excited to welcome new first-time contributors to our community and celebrate their contributions!
If you have always been interested &amp;amp; intrigued by open-source and LocalStack but don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start, then Hacktoberfest is a perfect place for you to start.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack Discussion Pages</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-06-08-announcing-localstack-discussion-pages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 12:51:11 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-06-08-announcing-localstack-discussion-pages/</guid><description>What a journey — we are delighted to see our LocalStack community grow across GitHub, Slack and social media platforms like Twitter and LinkedIn on a daily basis. We receive lots of valuable feedback from our users, ranging from new feature requests for the LocalStack platform, bug reports, enhancements and code contributions from various developers distributed across our user base.
To better collaborate with our community and create a space where LocalStack users can share experiences and discuss topics in a discoverable manner, we are excited to introduce the all-new LocalStack Discussion Pages.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack — 40K stars, 90M pulls and an engaged community!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-22-localstack-40k-stars-90m-pulls-and-an-engaged-community/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 10:34:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-22-localstack-40k-stars-90m-pulls-and-an-engaged-community/</guid><description>LocalStack provides a local cloud development platform that simplifies developing, testing, and debugging cloud apps locally and across CI/CD. Our core emulation service which provides emulated LocalStack Cloud APIs (currently focused on AWS cloud), is shipped as a Docker image and is currently being used by a large and active open source community with over 100K active users worldwide.
We recently crossed 40,000 Stargazers over GitHub and hit a new milestone of over 90,000,000 Docker pulls.</description></item><item><title>Introducing LocalStack Cockpit</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-02-07-localstack-cockpit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 13:10:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-02-07-localstack-cockpit/</guid><description>The new LocalStack Cockpit is now available. LocalStack Cockpit is a fully-integrated desktop experience for our LocalStack users. It allows our users to control, access, and manage LocalStack with a click of a button. No matter if you are a seasoned LocalStack user or just starting up to use LocalStack, Cockpit helps you use LocalStack more effectively!
Getting started You can now download the LocalStack Cockpit from our website by signing up for our v0.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack: 30k stars, 40M pulls - and just getting started! 🚀</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2021-05-06-localstack-40k-stars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 14:48:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2021-05-06-localstack-40k-stars/</guid><description>While cloud environments offer great characteristics for production workloads (high scalability, reliability, cost efficiency), the dev experience often falls short due to the centralized, remote execution model of clouds.
Developers are faced with a slow and tedious code → deploy → test → redeploy → &amp;hellip; cycle and often find themselves packaging and uploading their serverless applications tens or hundreds of times a day. These inherent limitations and hurdles in developing cloud applications have caused some folks to compare the cloud to the new mainframe era.</description></item></channel></rss>