<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Solutions on</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/solutions/</link><description>Recent content in Solutions on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:56:25 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Emulation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/solutions/cloud-emulation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:56:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/solutions/cloud-emulation/</guid><description>Core Cloud Emulation LocalStack's cloud emulation technology provides a fully functional cloud stack on your local machine. Develop and test your cloud applications with the full cloud experience, but without the hassle of the remote cloud. Benefits Your local cloud sandbox for development, testing, and experimentation More than 60+ emulated AWS cloud services, running entirely on your local machine Provides the same APIs and services as the real cloud No need to upload your code to the cloud for testing and debugging Reduce the latency of your deploys - literally develop your apps offline Truly shift left - get productive with cloud dev from day 1 Start up LocalStack as a Docker container - up and running in seconds Run your workloads and tests against the local API endpoints No need to write hand-crafted mocks for your unit and integration tests Remove the barrier for cloud dev - no more tedious cloud approvals!</description></item><item><title>Cloud Emulation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/solutions/ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:56:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/solutions/ecosystem/</guid><description>Ecosystem The power of the cloud ecosystem, all in your local development platform with LocalStack. Benefits Leverage our growing system of integrations Native integrations with key tools and platforms - from Infrastructure-as-Code frameworks to CI systems We want to meet developers where they are - LocalStack fits seamlessly into your existing dev flow LocalStack can integrate with virtually every cloud tool, as it provides emulation on the API level A variety of tools, plugins, and CLI wrappers are provided to easily interact these integrations Extensions architecture - opening up the LocalStack platform for third-party plugins Ability to plug in new emulators for third-party APIs (e.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Emulation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/solutions/enterprise-integration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:56:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/solutions/enterprise-integration/</guid><description>Enterprise Integration Organization-wide observability and traceability of your enterprise cloud application workflow. With dedicated support to help you and your enterprise make the best of LocalStack. Benefits Detailed insights and traceability across the CI/CD pipeline Record all interactions happening throughout a CI build to get a detailed timeline of API calls and application states Select and drill into the state at a particular point of execution Correlate the timeline of API calls with state changes, to identify hot spots and defect root causes Custom integrations to fit into the Enterprise IT landscape SSO integration with your preferred authentication provider Offline version as well as self-hosting options of parts of the platform Custom emulators for additional APIs to be plugged into the LocalStack platform Dedicated technical support with SLAs Personalized and dedicated technical support for you and your teams Consulting for custom use cases and implementations Prioritization of feature requirements FAQ Any Questions?</description></item><item><title>Cloud Emulation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/solutions/team-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:56:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/solutions/team-collaboration/</guid><description>Team Collaboration Resolve the friction and improve productivity of your cloud development teams with LocalStack's advanced collaboration features that natively scale with your workflow. Benefits Local Cloud Pods - advanced persistence for sharing application state Store a persistent snapshot of your LocalStack instance Inject cloud pods from your team members into your own local instance Cloud Pods can be stored, shared, versioned - similar to git commits Enable collaborative debugging - working on the same application state Enhanced debuggability and full reproducibility across CI/CD Spin up LocalStack in your CI pipelines to run tests before pushing out changes to production Fully reproducible environments from local dev, across CI/CD, into prod Spin up ephemeral environments to test or showcase your changes Tracing and analytics to gain deep insights into your application and the usage of LocalStack Drill-down of most commonly used services and API calls Detailed audit log of interactions as well as API error codes in your app over time Browse and investigate the state of your Cloud Pods and the contained resources, including version history Investigate and correlate API call traces, to enable deep debugging within your team FAQ Any Questions?</description></item></channel></rss>