<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 16:11:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/overview/</guid><description>What is LocalStack? LocalStack provides an easy-to-use test/mocking framework for developing Cloud applications. It spins up a testing environment on your local machine that provides the same functionality and APIs as the real AWS cloud environment.
You can run your Lambda functions, store data to DynamoDB tables, feed events through Kinesis streams, put your application behind an API Gateway, and much more. And all this happens on your local machine, without ever talking to the cloud.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 19:01:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/installation/</guid><description>Prerequisites Docker: The recommended way of installing LocalStack is using Docker Python: Required to install the localstack command-line interface (CLI) Installation The easiest way to install LocalStack is via pip:
pip install localstack You can then list the available commands:
localstack --help Note: If the command localstack is not available after successfully installing the package, please ensure that the folder containing pip binaries is configured in your $PATH.</description></item><item><title>Starting Up</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/starting-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 17:25:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/starting-up/</guid><description>To start the LocalStack platform in your local Docker environment:
SERVICES=... localstack start The environment variable SERVICES is a comma-separated list of services (see available services here). We recommend limiting the list of services to start up (e.g., SERVICES=lambda,s3,cognito,rds), to keep a low memory footprint and optimize performance.
Please note: Starting with version 0.11.0, all services are exposed via a single edge service endpoint - http://localhost:4566 by default. (The old service-specific port numbers from previous releases are now deprecated and disabled.</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/configuration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 12:58:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/docs/getting-started/configuration/</guid><description>LocalStack provides a number of configuration options that can be set via environment variables. Following environment variables are available in LocalStack Pro.
DNS_ADDRESS DNS_ADDRESS configures the IP address that the local DNS server should be bound to (default: 0.0.0.0). Can be configured to avoid port clashes in case a DNS server is already running on localhost port 53. Set to 0 or false to avoid exposing DNS port altogether.
DNS_RESOLVE_IP DNS_RESOLVE_IP configures the IP address that AWS hostnames should resolve to for transparent execution mode (default: 127.</description></item></channel></rss>