<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jobs on</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/</link><description>Recent content in Jobs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:40:06 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Senior Frontend Engineer (Typescript/React)</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/senior-frontend-engineer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/senior-frontend-engineer/</guid><description>Engagement: Full-time Experience level: Senior, Lead Role: Frontend Engineer Location: Remote (+-5 CET) | Vienna (AT) or Zürich (CH) About LocalStack We are a young, fast-growing startup, headquartered in Zurich, Switzerland, with a development office in Vienna, Austria and remote team members from around the world. At LocalStack, we’re building world-class tooling to support highly efficient dev&amp;test loops for cloud application developers. Our core product is the LocalStack cloud emulator - a light-weight cloud sandbox running in Docker that allows our users to develop cloud applications entirely on their local machines.</description></item><item><title>Technical Key Account Manager</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/technical-key-account-manager/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 08:40:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/technical-key-account-manager/</guid><description>About You Are you an entrepreneurial-minded go-to-market leader with a passion for nurturing lasting relationships with high-value customers to ensure mutual long-term success? Do you naturally take ownership, drive and embrace innovation? Are you looking for a rare opportunity to come in and build the strategy, framework, and processes required to quickly build and scale the go-to-market function of a high-growth global tech startup? If that’s you, you may be the driving force we’re looking for.</description></item><item><title>Senior/Lead Support Engineer</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/lead-support-engineer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 13:40:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/lead-support-engineer/</guid><description>About LocalStack We are a young, fast-growing startup, headquartered in Zurich, Switzerland, with a development office in Vienna, Austria and remote team members from around the world. At LocalStack, we’re building world-class tooling to support highly efficient dev&amp;test loops for cloud application developers. Our core product is the LocalStack cloud emulator - a light-weight cloud sandbox running in Docker that allows our users to develop cloud applications entirely on their local machines.</description></item><item><title>Support Engineer</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/support-engineer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 13:40:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/support-engineer/</guid><description>About LocalStack We are a young, fast-growing startup, headquartered in Zurich, Switzerland, with a development office in Vienna, Austria and remote team members from around the world. At LocalStack, we’re building world-class tooling to support highly efficient dev&amp;test loops for cloud application developers. Our core product is the LocalStack cloud emulator - a light-weight cloud sandbox running in Docker that allows our users to develop cloud applications entirely on their local machines.</description></item><item><title>Executive Assistant - BizOps, HR &amp; Finance</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/bizops-assistant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 13:40:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/bizops-assistant/</guid><description>About You Are you a highly organized and self-motivated individual who thrives in dynamic environments? Can you dive deep into new topics and enjoy to learn something new every day? Do you have a talent for prioritizing work and making sure that important things get done? Do you enjoy working in an international setting and finding solutions to a diverse set of problems? Can you see yourself as a driving force in helping scale a highly dynamic startup with a global customer base and a growing number of globally distributed employees?</description></item><item><title>Open Source Developer Advocate / DevRel Engineer</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/developer-advocate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 13:40:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/developer-advocate/</guid><description>Open Source Developer Advocate / DevRel Engineer About You Are you passionate about engaging with the developer community? Do you find yourself striking up interesting conversations about technology topics, the culture in engineering organizations, and the impact developers have on the companies they work for? Do you keep yourself up to date on all the new tools and stacks in the cloud&amp;AI space, with the ability to jump between different tech discussions about the entire DevSecOps cycle at the drop of a hat?</description></item><item><title>Backend/Python Developer</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/backend-python-developer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:40:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/jobs/backend-python-developer/</guid><description>Backend/Python Developer LocalStack, the flagship project for local dev&amp;test of Cloud applications (29k+ stars on Github, and several Fortune 500 customers) is looking for a top-notch backend/Python developer to help take the platform to the next level. This is a truly unique opportunity to work with the global developer community and shape the future of cloud application development. Requirements The ideal candidate will have strong experience in all or most of these areas: DevOps automation REST APIs Docker / containerization Software testing Python mocking/patching Unix/system engineering Experience with Cloud platforms (AWS/Azure/GCP) Responsibilities The main tasks and responsibilities will include: Develop new APIs and optimize existing features in LocalStack Help triaging / reproducing user issues and work on fixes and improvements Take ownership of implementing new strategic features on the platform Use data analytics and AI / Machine Learning to derive insights from large amounts of customer data Work Setting This is a fully remote position, with flexible working hours.</description></item></channel></rss>