<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Announcing LocalStack 2.0 General Availability!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-03-29-announcing-localstack-2.0-general-availability/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 09:35:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-03-29-announcing-localstack-2.0-general-availability/</guid><description>Last year we announced the general availability of LocalStack 1.0, our first major release, to help development teams propel their productivity by developing &amp;amp; testing their cloud applications locally! Between then and now, LocalStack has achieved significant adoption and amassed over 135 million Docker pulls and thousands of new customers worldwide! As we continue to execute our vision of making LocalStack the go-to platform for local cloud development, we are excited to announce our latest major release!</description></item><item><title>LocalStack and AWS Parity Explained</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-04-parity-explained/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-04-parity-explained/</guid><description>Parity for LocalStack means that when you, as a cloud developer, make an AWS API call to LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s cloud emulator, it behaves the same way AWS would.
Keeping parity with AWS has been our mission at LocalStack since day one. This is essential for building a reliable cloud emulator that provides a great experience for cloud application developers.
Recently we introduced new mechanisms to scale the endeavor and ensure that the parity of LocalStack with AWS increases continuously over time while keeping our service implementations up-to-date.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Pods - Enabling state sharing and team collaboration for local cloud development</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-26-cloud-pods/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-26-cloud-pods/</guid><description>📢 Cloud Pods have seen a lot of improvements since this blog post was published. We have deprecated the commit and inject commands in favour of the new save and load commands. We have also made Cloud Pods available to our Community &amp;amp; Pro users. For more information, please refer to our documentation. Background: Ephemeral and persistent state in LocalStack By default, the state of all services in LocalStack is ephemeral - i.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack Extensions</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:51:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</guid><description>With the LocalStack 1.0 General Availability going live last month, we announced LocalStack Extensions! LocalStack Extensions allow users to extend and customize LocalStack using pluggable Python distributions.
Setting up LocalStack Extensions LocalStack Extensions is part of our Pro offering. To get started with using LocalStack Extensions, first log in to your account using the LocalStack CLI:
$ localstack login Please provide your login credentials below Username: .</description></item><item><title>Introducing LocalStack Desktop Application for local cloud development &amp; testing</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-09-introducing-localstack-desktop-application-for-local-cloud-development-testing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-09-introducing-localstack-desktop-application-for-local-cloud-development-testing/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that we have released an all-new Desktop Application to make cloud development with LocalStack a breeze! The Desktop application underscores our unwavering commitment to make LocalStack accessible for our users, who would like to use a local cloud sandbox for development, testing, and experimentation, and truly embrace the inner dev loop. LocalStack enables users to control, manage, and visualize over 80+ emulated AWS cloud services, running entirely on your local machine.</description></item><item><title>Join LocalStack at AWS re:Invent 2023</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-09-join-localstack-at-aws-reinvent-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-09-join-localstack-at-aws-reinvent-2023/</guid><description>LocalStack is excited to be participating in AWS re:Invent 2023, Amazon&amp;rsquo;s premier annual cloud computing conference. Amidst keynote addresses, an array of technical sessions, and a bustling expo floor designed for learning and networking, we&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce our role as an Exhibit Sponsor for this year&amp;rsquo;s event.
Join us at Booth #1074 (Map) in the Venetian Expo, Las Vegas, from November 27 to December 1. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportune moment to engage with the LocalStack team, where we&amp;rsquo;ll not only share our insights but also learn valuable lessons from your experiences.</description></item><item><title>OpenFABR leverages LocalStack for local Infrastructure as Code development and validation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-25-case-study-openfabr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-25-case-study-openfabr/</guid><description>“LocalStack has revolutionized our development process by providing seamless Infrastructure-as-Code validation, rapid resource spin-up, and streamlined testing. It&amp;rsquo;s an essential component of our development toolkit and has greatly enhanced our team&amp;rsquo;s agility &amp;amp; efficiency.”
Janaka Abeywardhana,
Co-Founder — CPTO at FABR
FABR is a cloud infrastructure and tooling company that addresses critical challenges in building and managing cloud infrastructure for application development across multiple public cloud providers.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack has joined AWS Marketplace to streamline local cloud development &amp; testing!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-07-localstack-has-joined-aws-marketplace-to-streamline-local-cloud-development-testing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-07-localstack-has-joined-aws-marketplace-to-streamline-local-cloud-development-testing/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that LocalStack is now available in the AWS Marketplace. LocalStack is the leading platform for local development and testing of cloud applications. LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Emulator allows you to effectively run over 80 AWS services directly on your local machine and on CI/CD systems to significantly cut down on development time and feedback cycles. At its core, LocalStack provides a growing ecosystem of native integrations that encompasses crucial components such as CI/CD providers, application development frameworks, programming language SDKs, Infrastructure-as-Code tools, and more.</description></item><item><title>Xiatech accelerates their development workflows on cloud using LocalStack!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-07-05-case-study-xiatech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-07-05-case-study-xiatech/</guid><description>“Our engineering team utilizes LocalStack to provide a complete, localized AWS environment where developers can build, test, profile and debug infrastructure and code ahead of deployment to the cloud.”
Rick Timmis,
Head of Engineering at Xiatech
Xiatech helps organizations and users connect systems, unify data, and make data-driven decisions with artificial intelligence via a continuous flow of actionable insights. Xiatech’s flagship platform is Xfuze, a hyper-integration platform that helps customers gain key insights, create value from data and turbocharge legacy technology investments.</description></item><item><title>Develop your Cloudflare Workers + AWS apps locally with LocalStack &amp; Miniflare</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-06-26-develop-your-cloudflare-workers-aws-apps-locally-with-localstack-miniflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-06-26-develop-your-cloudflare-workers-aws-apps-locally-with-localstack-miniflare/</guid><description>LocalStack is a cloud development platform that turbocharges your cloud application development &amp;amp; testing, fosters team collaboration, and provides an integrated cloud developer experience with a local cloud sandbox. LocalStack’s core cloud emulator runs inside a Docker container and provides a set of external network ports for integrations, SDKs, or CI providers for developers to execute their cloud &amp;amp; serverless applications fully locally without talking to the real cloud services. This enables a highly efficient development loop, by reducing the feedback cycles from minutes to seconds.</description></item></channel></rss>