<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Test Monitoring for LocalStack Apps</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2021-09-16-test-monitoring-for-localstack-apps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 13:10:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2021-09-16-test-monitoring-for-localstack-apps/</guid><description>LocalStack gives developers the freedom to develop their cloud applications locally (even offline) - enabling a highly efficient dev&amp;amp;test loop. It also helps prevent scary cloud bills at the end of every month! LocalStack has an amazing community of users, contributors, and supporters - and generally demonstrates a very strong commitment to supporting open source.
The community uses LocalStack for many use cases such as developing microservice cloud applications. One of the strongest use cases why developers use LocalStack is “testing”.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack: 30k stars, 40M pulls - and just getting started! 🚀</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2021-05-06-localstack-40k-stars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 14:48:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2021-05-06-localstack-40k-stars/</guid><description>While cloud environments offer great characteristics for production workloads (high scalability, reliability, cost efficiency), the dev experience often falls short due to the centralized, remote execution model of clouds.
Developers are faced with a slow and tedious code → deploy → test → redeploy → &amp;hellip; cycle and often find themselves packaging and uploading their serverless applications tens or hundreds of times a day. These inherent limitations and hurdles in developing cloud applications have caused some folks to compare the cloud to the new mainframe era.</description></item></channel></rss>