<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LocalStack x Gitpod - Run cloud applications with LocalStack and Gitpod</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-26-localstack-x-gitpod-run-cloud-applications-with-localstack-and-gitpod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 11:31:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-26-localstack-x-gitpod-run-cloud-applications-with-localstack-and-gitpod/</guid><description>Shipping applications to production requires them to be battle-tested in the dev environment. The dev environment should mimic the production environment as closely as possible. This comes with a cost: testing cloud applications is cumbersome as they have many moving parts. For instance, if you build a simple Lambda function in AWS, you might use services such as CloudWatch, S3, IAM, etc.
Imagine configuring your project and provisioning these cloud resources in a test environment every time for developing new features.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack Extensions</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:51:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</guid><description>With the LocalStack 1.0 General Availability going live last month, we announced LocalStack Extensions! LocalStack Extensions allow users to extend and customize LocalStack using pluggable Python distributions.
Setting up LocalStack Extensions LocalStack Extensions is part of our Pro offering. To get started with using LocalStack Extensions, first log in to your account using the LocalStack CLI:
$ localstack login Please provide your login credentials below Username: .</description></item><item><title>Cloud Pods - Enabling state sharing and team collaboration for local cloud development</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-26-cloud-pods/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-26-cloud-pods/</guid><description>Background: Ephemeral and persistent state in LocalStack By default, the state of all services in LocalStack is ephemeral - i.e., whenever you restart the LocalStack Docker container, it presents a fresh instance with a clean state that can be used to create your application resources locally. This is the default mode, which is optimized for quick experimentation, and frequent container restarts, making sure to always start with a clean slate.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack and AWS Parity Explained</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-04-parity-explained/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-04-parity-explained/</guid><description>Parity for LocalStack means that when you, as a cloud developer, make an AWS API call to LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s cloud emulator, it behaves the same way AWS would.
Keeping parity with AWS has been our mission at LocalStack since day one. This is essential for building a reliable cloud emulator that provides a great experience for cloud application developers.
Recently we introduced new mechanisms to scale the endeavor and ensure that the parity of LocalStack with AWS increases continuously over time while keeping our service implementations up-to-date.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack 1.0 General Availability!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-07-13-announcing-localstack-v1-general-availability/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 11:00:55 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-07-13-announcing-localstack-v1-general-availability/</guid><description>Today, we are excited to announce the general availability of LocalStack 1.0. This major release is a significant milestone towards our vision to propel developer productivity - by allowing dev teams to quickly and conveniently develop &amp;amp; test their cloud applications locally and across the CI/CD pipeline.
At LocalStack, we&amp;rsquo;re working to provide a better way to develop and test your cloud applications. Our platform is redefining cloud development by enabling a highly efficient, fully local development &amp;amp; testing loop and giving developers back control over their environments.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack Discussion Pages</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-06-08-announcing-localstack-discussion-pages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 12:51:11 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-06-08-announcing-localstack-discussion-pages/</guid><description>What a journey — we are delighted to see our LocalStack community grow across GitHub, Slack and social media platforms like Twitter and LinkedIn on a daily basis. We receive lots of valuable feedback from our users, ranging from new feature requests for the LocalStack platform, bug reports, enhancements and code contributions from various developers distributed across our user base.
To better collaborate with our community and create a space where LocalStack users can share experiences and discuss topics in a discoverable manner, we are excited to introduce the all-new LocalStack Discussion Pages.</description></item><item><title>Monitor your failing Lambdas with CloudWatch and LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-25-cloudwatch-metric-alarms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-25-cloudwatch-metric-alarms/</guid><description>AWS CloudWatch is a service that enables monitoring of your AWS infrastructure by collecting logs and operational metrics of your deployment. An integral part of infrastructure operations is reacting in real-time to anomalous changes in metrics, e.g., spiking disk or CPU usage or failures in your serverless functions. This is where CloudWatch metric alarms and actions come into play, which you can now develop and test using LocalStack!</description></item><item><title>Debug Lambda functions from your IDE using LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-09-debug-your-lamda-functions-from-your-ide-using-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 05:08:41 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-09-debug-your-lamda-functions-from-your-ide-using-localstack/</guid><description>In the previous blog, we checked out how to hot-swap Lambda functions locally using LocalStack. Using LocalStack, you can execute your Lambda functions locally without the need to deploy them to AWS. This is a great way to test your code and learn more about how your Lambda functions work before deploying them to AWS. But there is always a question about debugging the Lambda functions from your IDE before deploying it.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack — 40K stars, 90M pulls and an engaged community!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-22-localstack-40k-stars-90m-pulls-and-an-engaged-community/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 10:34:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-22-localstack-40k-stars-90m-pulls-and-an-engaged-community/</guid><description>LocalStack provides a local cloud development platform that simplifies developing, testing, and debugging cloud apps locally and across CI/CD. Our core emulation service which provides emulated LocalStack Cloud APIs (currently focused on AWS cloud), is shipped as a Docker image and is currently being used by a large and active open source community with over 100K active users worldwide.
We recently crossed 40,000 Stargazers over GitHub and hit a new milestone of over 90,000,000 Docker pulls.</description></item><item><title>Develop and Test Real-time Data Pipelines with LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-04-develop-and-test-data-analytics-pipelines-on-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-04-develop-and-test-data-analytics-pipelines-on-localstack/</guid><description>At LocalStack, we rely on AWS Lambda as a key part of our serverless infrastructure toolkit. As with any critical service, we want to extract analytics event data from running Lambda functions and aggregate it in our data warehouse so that we can track user stories and squash bugs. But this presents a challenge: how can we emit detailed analytics data while keeping Lambda code simple and performant?</description></item></channel></rss>