<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Products on</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/products/</link><description>Recent content in Products on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:56:25 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Emulation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/products/emulation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:56:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/products/emulation/</guid><description>LocalStack Cloud Emulation LocalStack provides a fully functional local cloud stack - develop your cloud apps offline! Get started now! Truly shift left - get productive with cloud dev from day 1 Start up LocalStack as a Docker container - up and running in seconds Provides the same APIs as the real cloud, all on your local machine No need to write hand-crafted mocks for your unit and integration tests Reduce the latency of your deploys - literally develop your apps offline Remove the barrier for cloud dev - no more tedious cloud approvals!</description></item><item><title>Enterprise</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/products/enterprise/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:56:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/products/enterprise/</guid><description>LocalStack Team / Enterprise Advanced use cases and collaboration features that natively scale with your development team Contact us now! Advanced persistence with Local Cloud Pods Store a persistent snapshot of your LocalStack instance to capture the state Inject the snapshot into your local instance to restore the state Enable collaborative debugging - working on the same application state Cloud Pods can be stored, shared, versioned - similar to git commits Bootstrap and replicate environments in your CI builds Configure your application state to preseed the test environment Continuously track the state of your LocalStack instance during a CI build Easily replicate the CI state into your environment for local debugging Get a representative copy of production mirrored into your test environment Insights and traceability across the CI/CD pipeline Easily keep track of the state in your LocalStack instance for each CI build Visually browse and inspect the state at different phases of execution Use the diff view to compare the delta between two points in time Collect aggregated statistics and insights of your CI builds over time</description></item><item><title>LocalStack Cockpit</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/products/cockpit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:25:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/products/cockpit/</guid><description>LocalStack Cockpit LocalStack Cockpit, a fully-integrated desktop experience for LocalStack. Start using LocalStack, without the fuss Learn more Download Control LocalStack without the fuss Start and Stop your LocalStack instance with a click of a button See the current status of your LocalStack instance Easily accessible via a tray icon Initialization checks to see if your setup is correct Quick links to our website, documentation and the Web App Instant insights See runtime and environment information on the info page See available services and their status on the service page See log information of the LocalStack instance Manage your LocalStack configurations Directly manage and use your profiles (run configurations) See available services and their status on the service page See log information of the LocalStack instance Download LocalStack Cockpit Version: Latest: v0.</description></item></channel></rss>