<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Harsh Mishra on LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/contributors/harsh-mishra/</link><description>Recent content in Harsh Mishra on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/contributors/harsh-mishra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Announcing LocalStack Extensions</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:51:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</guid><description>With the LocalStack 1.0 General Availability going live last month, we announced LocalStack Extensions! LocalStack Extensions allow users to extend and customize LocalStack using pluggable Python distributions.
Setting up LocalStack Extensions LocalStack Extensions is part of our Pro offering. To get started with using LocalStack Extensions, first log in to your account using the LocalStack CLI:
$ localstack login Please provide your login credentials below Username: .</description></item><item><title>Introducing LocalStack Docker Extension for Docker Desktop</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-01-13-introducing-localstack-extension-for-docker-desktop/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-01-13-introducing-localstack-extension-for-docker-desktop/</guid><description>We are excited to announce the release of the LocalStack Docker Extension to help developers run their cloud &amp;amp; serverless applications locally. With our Docker Extension, developers can capitalize on a fully-integrated experience to manage their LocalStack image, configuration profiles, and container logs directly within the Docker Desktop. Docker Extensions was officially announced last year to help communities integrate new functionalities with the Docker Desktop, and we have worked closely with the Docker team to develop our extension!</description></item><item><title>Contribute to Open Source With LocalStack &amp; Hacktoberfest</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-10-01-contribute-to-open-source-with-localstack-hacktoberfest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-10-01-contribute-to-open-source-with-localstack-hacktoberfest/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s October 2022, and we have a few surprises already in store for our open-source community. LocalStack is participating in Hacktoberfest 2022, a month-long open-source program to promote and bolster open-source contribution and collaboration! We are opening up projects to contribute to for our first Hacktoberfest, and we are incredibly excited to welcome new first-time contributors to our community and celebrate their contributions!
If you have always been interested &amp;amp; intrigued by open-source and LocalStack but don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start, then Hacktoberfest is a perfect place for you to start.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack Discussion Pages</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-06-08-announcing-localstack-discussion-pages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 12:51:11 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-06-08-announcing-localstack-discussion-pages/</guid><description>What a journey — we are delighted to see our LocalStack community grow across GitHub, Slack and social media platforms like Twitter and LinkedIn on a daily basis. We receive lots of valuable feedback from our users, ranging from new feature requests for the LocalStack platform, bug reports, enhancements and code contributions from various developers distributed across our user base.
To better collaborate with our community and create a space where LocalStack users can share experiences and discuss topics in a discoverable manner, we are excited to introduce the all-new LocalStack Discussion Pages.</description></item><item><title>Debug Lambda functions from your IDE using LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-09-debug-your-lamda-functions-from-your-ide-using-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 05:08:41 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-05-09-debug-your-lamda-functions-from-your-ide-using-localstack/</guid><description>In the previous blog, we checked out how to hot-swap Lambda functions locally using LocalStack. Using LocalStack, you can execute your Lambda functions locally without the need to deploy them to AWS. This is a great way to test your code and learn more about how your Lambda functions work before deploying them to AWS. But there is always a question about debugging the Lambda functions from your IDE before deploying it.</description></item><item><title>Hot Swapping Python Lambda Functions using LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-03-07-hot-swapping-python-lambda-functions-using-localstack/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 08:53:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-03-07-hot-swapping-python-lambda-functions-using-localstack/</guid><description>AWS Lambda is a Serverless Function as a Service (FaaS) system that allows you to write code in your favorite programming language and run it on the AWS ecosystem. Unlike deploying your code on a server, you can now break down your application into many independent functions and deploy them as a singular units. With the help of AWS Lambda, you can strive for more modular code that can be tested and debugged while integrated with the AWS infrastructure and your core system.</description></item></channel></rss>