<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thomas on LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/contributors/thomas/</link><description>Recent content in Thomas on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:51:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/contributors/thomas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LocalStack and AWS Parity Explained</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-04-parity-explained/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-08-04-parity-explained/</guid><description>Parity for LocalStack means that when you, as a cloud developer, make an AWS API call to LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s cloud emulator, it behaves the same way AWS would.
Keeping parity with AWS has been our mission at LocalStack since day one. This is essential for building a reliable cloud emulator that provides a great experience for cloud application developers.
Recently we introduced new mechanisms to scale the endeavor and ensure that the parity of LocalStack with AWS increases continuously over time while keeping our service implementations up-to-date.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack Extensions</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:51:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-09-12-announcing-localstack-extensions/</guid><description>With the LocalStack 1.0 General Availability going live last month, we announced LocalStack Extensions! LocalStack Extensions allow users to extend and customize LocalStack using pluggable Python distributions.
Setting up LocalStack Extensions LocalStack Extensions is part of our Pro offering. To get started with using LocalStack Extensions, first log in to your account using the LocalStack CLI:
$ localstack login Please provide your login credentials below Username: .</description></item></channel></rss>