<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Application on LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/tags/application/</link><description>Recent content in Application on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/tags/application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/7-invoices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/7-invoices/</guid><description>You can find your entire invoice history in your account details at Account billing section.
Please note, if you are part of an organization account, only your organization’s admins have access to the billing section.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/8-cancel-trial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/8-cancel-trial/</guid><description>Your free trial will automatically expire after 14 days - no need to manually cancel it. We do not automatically add a paid license at the end of the free trial.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/9-more-licenses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/9-more-licenses/</guid><description>You can create new subscriptions on Account billing section by using the + ADD NEW PLAN button.
Please note, if you are part of an organization account, only your organization’s admins have access to the billing section and can assign API keys to you in the member section at Account members section.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/e-ci-credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/e-ci-credits/</guid><description>Your CI key offers a certain monthly number of available credits, depending on the number of individual user seats you have purchased. Each subscription (both Pro and Team) comes with the number of chosen individual developer keys to be configured on each developer&amp;rsquo;s machine, plus one extra CI key (at no additional charge) which allows you to use LocalStack in your CI environment.
For example, if you have purchased 8 Pro seats, the CI key would come with 200 CI credits (100 base credits for the first three users and 20 additional credits for each user 4-10).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://localstack.cloud/faq/f-ci-credits-consumed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/faq/f-ci-credits-consumed/</guid><description>Every activation of a CI key consumes one build credit. This means that every build in a CI environment which spins up the LocalStack container will consume one credit.</description></item></channel></rss>