<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The LocalStack Team on LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/contributors/localstack-team/</link><description>Recent content in The LocalStack Team on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 14:48:49 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/contributors/localstack-team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Announcing LocalStack 3.0 General Availability!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-16-announcing-localstack-30-general-availability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-16-announcing-localstack-30-general-availability/</guid><description>Today, we are excited to announce LocalStack 3.0, our latest major release aiming to empower developers with a high-fidelity local cloud development &amp;amp; testing experience. Earlier this year, we unveiled LocalStack 2.0, which brought forth many new features and improvements, along with better integration with the AWS tooling ecosystem. With the 3.0 release, we’re doubling down on our promise to boost developer productivity and tackle the issues that often slow down cloud software development and delivery workflows — specifically, simplifying onboarding and eliminating the inefficiencies that lead to prolonged development and test cycles.</description></item><item><title>Introducing LocalStack Desktop Application for local cloud development &amp; testing</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-09-introducing-localstack-desktop-application-for-local-cloud-development-testing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-09-introducing-localstack-desktop-application-for-local-cloud-development-testing/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that we have released an all-new Desktop Application to make cloud development with LocalStack a breeze! The Desktop application underscores our unwavering commitment to make LocalStack accessible for our users, who would like to use a local cloud sandbox for development, testing, and experimentation, and truly embrace the inner dev loop. LocalStack enables users to control, manage, and visualize over 80+ emulated AWS cloud services, running entirely on your local machine.</description></item><item><title>Join LocalStack at AWS re:Invent 2023</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-09-join-localstack-at-aws-reinvent-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-11-09-join-localstack-at-aws-reinvent-2023/</guid><description>LocalStack is excited to be participating in AWS re:Invent 2023, Amazon&amp;rsquo;s premier annual cloud computing conference. Amidst keynote addresses, an array of technical sessions, and a bustling expo floor designed for learning and networking, we&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce our role as an Exhibit Sponsor for this year&amp;rsquo;s event.
Join us at Booth #1074 (Map) in the Venetian Expo, Las Vegas, from November 27 to December 1. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportune moment to engage with the LocalStack team, where we&amp;rsquo;ll not only share our insights but also learn valuable lessons from your experiences.</description></item><item><title>OpenFABR leverages LocalStack for local Infrastructure as Code development and validation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-25-case-study-openfabr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-25-case-study-openfabr/</guid><description>“LocalStack has revolutionized our development process by providing seamless Infrastructure-as-Code validation, rapid resource spin-up, and streamlined testing. It&amp;rsquo;s an essential component of our development toolkit and has greatly enhanced our team&amp;rsquo;s agility &amp;amp; efficiency.”
Janaka Abeywardhana,
Co-Founder — CPTO at FABR
FABR is a cloud infrastructure and tooling company that addresses critical challenges in building and managing cloud infrastructure for application development across multiple public cloud providers.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack has joined AWS Marketplace to streamline local cloud development &amp; testing!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-07-localstack-has-joined-aws-marketplace-to-streamline-local-cloud-development-testing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-07-localstack-has-joined-aws-marketplace-to-streamline-local-cloud-development-testing/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that LocalStack is now available in the AWS Marketplace. LocalStack is the leading platform for local development and testing of cloud applications. LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Emulator allows you to effectively run over 80 AWS services directly on your local machine and on CI/CD systems to significantly cut down on development time and feedback cycles. At its core, LocalStack provides a growing ecosystem of native integrations that encompasses crucial components such as CI/CD providers, application development frameworks, programming language SDKs, Infrastructure-as-Code tools, and more.</description></item><item><title>Xiatech accelerates their development workflows on cloud using LocalStack!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-07-05-case-study-xiatech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-07-05-case-study-xiatech/</guid><description>“Our engineering team utilizes LocalStack to provide a complete, localized AWS environment where developers can build, test, profile and debug infrastructure and code ahead of deployment to the cloud.”
Rick Timmis,
Head of Engineering at Xiatech
Xiatech helps organizations and users connect systems, unify data, and make data-driven decisions with artificial intelligence via a continuous flow of actionable insights. Xiatech’s flagship platform is Xfuze, a hyper-integration platform that helps customers gain key insights, create value from data and turbocharge legacy technology investments.</description></item><item><title>KnowBe4 redefines their local cloud development &amp; testing using LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-04-24-case-study-knowbe4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-04-24-case-study-knowbe4/</guid><description>“LocalStack has been a game changer in terms of development speed and efficiency for our team migrating our monolithic application to a serverless Node.js stack on AWS.”
Kevin Breton,
VP of Engineering at KnowBe4
KCM GRC Platform by KnowBe4 is a governance, risk management, and compliance (GRC) software platform. Designed to help organizations move away from manual processes, KCM GRC efficiently manages risk and compliance by integrating with various third-party vendors.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack 2.0 General Availability!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-03-29-announcing-localstack-2.0-general-availability/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 09:35:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-03-29-announcing-localstack-2.0-general-availability/</guid><description>Last year we announced the general availability of LocalStack 1.0, our first major release, to help development teams propel their productivity by developing &amp;amp; testing their cloud applications locally! Between then and now, LocalStack has achieved significant adoption and amassed over 135 million Docker pulls and thousands of new customers worldwide! As we continue to execute our vision of making LocalStack the go-to platform for local cloud development, we are excited to announce our latest major release!</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack 1.0 General Availability!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-07-13-announcing-localstack-v1-general-availability/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 11:00:55 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-07-13-announcing-localstack-v1-general-availability/</guid><description>Today, we are excited to announce the general availability of LocalStack 1.0. This major release is a significant milestone towards our vision to propel developer productivity - by allowing dev teams to quickly and conveniently develop &amp;amp; test their cloud applications locally and across the CI/CD pipeline.
At LocalStack, we&amp;rsquo;re working to provide a better way to develop and test your cloud applications. Our platform is redefining cloud development by enabling a highly efficient, fully local development &amp;amp; testing loop and giving developers back control over their environments.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack — 40K stars, 90M pulls and an engaged community!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-22-localstack-40k-stars-90m-pulls-and-an-engaged-community/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 10:34:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-04-22-localstack-40k-stars-90m-pulls-and-an-engaged-community/</guid><description>LocalStack provides a local cloud development platform that simplifies developing, testing, and debugging cloud apps locally and across CI/CD. Our core emulation service which provides emulated LocalStack Cloud APIs (currently focused on AWS cloud), is shipped as a Docker image and is currently being used by a large and active open source community with over 100K active users worldwide.
We recently crossed 40,000 Stargazers over GitHub and hit a new milestone of over 90,000,000 Docker pulls.</description></item></channel></rss>