<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The LocalStack Team on</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/contributors/localstack-team/</link><description>Recent content in The LocalStack Team on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 14:48:49 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/contributors/localstack-team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hot Swapping Python Lambda Functions using LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-03-07-hot-swapping-python-lambda-functions-using-localstack/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 08:53:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-03-07-hot-swapping-python-lambda-functions-using-localstack/</guid><description>AWS Lambda is a Serverless Function as a Service (FaaS) system that allows you to write code in your favorite programming language and run it on the AWS ecosystem. Unlike deploying your code on a server, you can now break down your application into many independent functions and deploy them as a singular units. With the help of AWS Lambda, you can strive for more modular code that can be tested and debugged while integrated with the AWS infrastructure and your core system.</description></item><item><title>Introducing LocalStack Cockpit</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-02-07-localstack-cockpit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 13:10:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2022-02-07-localstack-cockpit/</guid><description>The new LocalStack Cockpit is now available. LocalStack Cockpit is a fully-integrated desktop experience for our LocalStack users. It allows our users to control, access, and manage LocalStack with a click of a button. No matter if you are a seasoned LocalStack user or just starting up to use LocalStack, Cockpit helps you use LocalStack more effectively!
Getting started You can now download the LocalStack Cockpit from our website by signing up for our v0.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack: 30k stars, 40M pulls - and just getting started! 🚀</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2021-05-06-localstack-40k-stars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 14:48:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2021-05-06-localstack-40k-stars/</guid><description>While cloud environments offer great characteristics for production workloads (high scalability, reliability, cost efficiency), the dev experience often falls short due to the centralized, remote execution model of clouds.
Developers are faced with a slow and tedious code → deploy → test → redeploy → &amp;hellip; cycle and often find themselves packaging and uploading their serverless applications tens or hundreds of times a day. These inherent limitations and hurdles in developing cloud applications have caused some folks to compare the cloud to the new mainframe era.</description></item></channel></rss>