<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>case-study on LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/tags/case-study/</link><description>Recent content in case-study on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localstack.cloud/tags/case-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>OpenFABR leverages LocalStack for Infrastructure as Code for local development &amp; validation</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-25-case-study-openfabr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-09-25-case-study-openfabr/</guid><description>“LocalStack has revolutionized our development process by providing seamless Infrastructure-as-Code validation, rapid resource spin-up, and streamlined testing. It&amp;rsquo;s an essential component of our development toolkit and has greatly enhanced our team&amp;rsquo;s agility &amp;amp; efficiency.”
Janaka Abeywardhana,
Co-Founder — CPTO at FABR
FABR is a cloud infrastructure and tooling company that addresses critical challenges in building and managing cloud infrastructure for application development across multiple public cloud providers.</description></item><item><title>Xiatech accelerates their development workflows on cloud using LocalStack!</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-07-05-case-study-xiatech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-07-05-case-study-xiatech/</guid><description>“Our engineering team utilizes LocalStack to provide a complete, localized AWS environment where developers can build, test, profile and debug infrastructure and code ahead of deployment to the cloud.”
Rick Timmis,
Head of Engineering at Xiatech
Xiatech helps organizations and users connect systems, unify data, and make data-driven decisions with artificial intelligence via a continuous flow of actionable insights. Xiatech’s flagship platform is Xfuze, a hyper-integration platform that helps customers gain key insights, create value from data and turbocharge legacy technology investments.</description></item><item><title>KnowBe4 redefines their local cloud development &amp; testing using LocalStack</title><link>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-04-24-case-study-knowbe4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://localstack.cloud/blog/2023-04-24-case-study-knowbe4/</guid><description>“LocalStack has been a game changer in terms of development speed and efficiency for our team migrating our monolithic application to a serverless Node.js stack on AWS.”
Kevin Breton,
VP of Engineering at KnowBe4
KCM GRC Platform by KnowBe4 is a governance, risk management, and compliance (GRC) software platform. Designed to help organizations move away from manual processes, KCM GRC efficiently manages risk and compliance by integrating with various third-party vendors.</description></item></channel></rss>